That was pretty close, Shido. Are you okay?
Mana? I...
Right. This is probably a little shocking, huh?
Excuse me, but we were in the middle of a lovely date, and I find it terribly rude of you to interrupt us like this.
Give me just a minute, big brother. This won't take very long.
Go to me!
Stop it! Don't kill her!
I knew it. You really are a good, Shido.
Mana, why?
How can you stand there like nothing happened? You just killed a person!
I just killed a spirit.
Besides, I do this all the time.
It is something all things are given.
It cannot be bought, and it cannot be sold.
People often waste it, hold it dear, and chase after it.
If only we knew what it was.
It cannot be bought, and it cannot be bought.
If only we knew what it was, it cannot be bought.
Thank you.
Shido!
What happened?
We've been looking for you.
Spill it.
What's going on?
Oh no.
You've been hurt.
I'm so sorry.
Did I make it worse?
No.
Sorry.
Shido!
Hey.
Is your arm feeling any better?
Yeah.
Good.
We can go then.
Wait.
Go where exactly?
We're continuing our date, silly.
Can I have some bread, please?
Corn dogs!
See pork buns!
Here.
Thanks.
That was sweet.
Come on, let's go!
Hold on!
Tolka.
I don't have much money on me.
Don't worry about money.
Reyna let me borrow her magic buy things card.
You mean credit card?
She also told me about you and Kurumi and Mana.
I see.
Then...
You know I have to stop Kurumi from killing more people.
No?
No.
That's right?
Yeah, no.
No, no.
No.
I'm not Wow.
yeah i'm just i'm not sure how i should go about it with her i mean kurumi's a spirit but
she's different from you or yoshino now that isn't true at all and you know it
kurumi and i are the same we are
remember that i had you here for me you saved me i didn't even know i needed you but i did
then you asked me out on a date like today and showed me how amazing and beautiful this world
really is if it weren't for you shido i most likely would have ended up just like kurumi
there's only one difference between the two of us and that is having someone close who's reaching
out his hand toka thank you you've helped me realize what's important yeah does that mean
you aren't scared no not quite don't worry i'll be here to protect you thanks that makes me feel
better i know right shido can we stay like this for a while longer sure
well good morning shido how are you today
i'm fine you are so dead dude how dare you show your face around here that is i don't know lame
hold it please leave shido alone let's just go this way i have to admit i'm a little surprised
i thought for sure you wouldn't want to come to school today you know after all that crazy
drama kurumi that's me so you know i've made the decision that i need to save you
well that's kind of a strange thing to say i will not let you kill anyone else
else i will also not let mana kill you
how very big of you
i
little shido i've made the decision i need to test you and see if you're
really telling me the truth
ratatasker huh i can't believe you and my big brother are part of that twisted organization
i'm surprised you found that out now what do you want it's about shido
you're negligent at best how could you send him unarmed to go meet with dangerous spirits
you're a failure as a little sister so i'm going to take over that role from now on oh you've got to
be kidding me and let a corrupt company like deus ex machina get their hands on him i don't think so
mana how did you know you should stop underestimating me i know that except for ratatasker your little
group supplies all the military forces around the world with realizers and you you're one of their
employees who was sent to the ast
here he goes kurumi has not been seen leaving the school as of yet still though our real problem
is whether or not she'll listen to what we have to say hey where's kotari something just came up
she'll be back soon but this time i'll have to be your navigator okay got it let's do this
what happened we're analyzing right now i'm not going to stand here and listen to you call us
corrupt you know nothing about dem that place gave me a reason to live after i lost my memory
i can't thank them enough for their help really even after what they did to you what are you talking
about i've discovered something terrible from mana takamiya's cup what they've done is wrong her body
has been implanted with far too much magical power sadly she's not likely to live more than 10 years
you don't know they haven't told you
it's kotari what's up commander there's an intense spirit wave reaction at shido's high school
it's coming from kurumi tokasaki understood
it's a wide area barrier the kind of barrier meant to debilitate everyone within its range she did
this but why hey shido toka are you all right well my body feels heavy for some reason why am i the only
one who's not affected since you've sealed the powers of both toka and yoshino it's like you've
received their divine protection given these conditions you're the only one who can move
normally
shido darling can you hear me if you need anything at all feel free to join me on the roof something
tells me you might want to get here as soon as possible though
listen to me stay right here okay and don't worry i'm going to save her be careful shido
identifying ast origami tobiichi
one basic realizer activate at once
i'm glad you were so eager to come see me
i'm showing you're using the emergency uniform what's going on dangerous situation i need support
hello origami you seem like you're in a rush where might you be off to i'm here to protect shido from
you no that doesn't work for me terribly sorry but you'll have to stay right here
oh shido don't go
it's not safe to go up there alone shido come on get up
move
there you go toka i can do it
hey who did that
kurumi good morning toka going anywhere
kurumi what is all of this about isn't it pretty my time eating castle
this barrier sucks up the time from anyone who steps on my shadow
the time your eyes a clock that's right what you're looking at is my time lovely thing i suppose you
could call it my lifespan my angel has such a wonderful power but unfortunately it does have
that nasty habit of eating up my time whenever i use it so i have to replenish it with other people's
time every once in a while what other people's time everyone is my pitiful adorable prey
but you you're special shido and you don't even realize it guess what
you're the reason i'm here i came all this way just so i could become one with you in person and see
the look on your face when i eat you okay fine i'm the one you want so don't hurt everyone else
i'll think about that option but first i want you to take back what you said this morning
obviously you're not going to save me now are you come on shido don't you think i'm downright
awful to cause all this pain for such a silly reason you can say it you hate me and it's clear
to you that i'm not someone who deserves mercy i will eat you but first i'm giving you the chance to
take your words back do that darling and i'll reward you by taking down this barrier so those people
won't die so what will it be shido better make your decision quickly or there will be nothing left for
you to save take down the barrier kurumi do it but i will not give up on you why are you so stubborn
your choices confuse me
you know what that sound means so what could i possibly be doing it's the spatial quake alarm
a quake she can't can she she's causing a spatial quake on purpose we didn't know any spirit could do
that what is my little shido going to do if a spatial quake occurs now what do you imagine will
happen to all those unconscious students shin kurumi's emotional condition has started changing it seems
almost as if she's frightened of you that's it listen you've been saying you came here just so you
could eat me right if that's true stop the quake if you don't stop it
i'll jump off this roof and kill myself you're making yourself a hostage nice threat but something
tells me you're not going to follow through with it watch me are you kidding me damn it that was
incredibly stupid i'm not as stupid as you think because now i know i have worth to you as a hostage
if you could go ahead and stop the spatial quake that'd be great oh and take down the barrier while
you're at it if you refuse i swear i'll kill myself this is ridiculous
oh there is one more thing how much more can there be i want you to allow yourself to have another
chance are we back to this trust me i'm more trouble than i'm worth that isn't true even for you
listen to me you can change and be happy if you want and i know you do
i know it if that wasn't an option you wouldn't have had so much fun on our date
you're wrong it's too late it's not too late i can help you yes you'll have to live with what
you've done for the rest of your life but still kurumi it doesn't matter how terrible you've been
nothing will ever give me a reason not to save you what i i don't know
why are you so kind am i worth it can't i
it doesn't really work for us to have you fall for his pretty words you know
look thank you so much shito well that's that why don't you go take a rest now
goodness me what kurumi but how it seems to me i chose for this endeavor might have
been a little too young
but now why don't we put a stop to this tediousness already
hi are you ever not in trouble big brother right on time like usual
you've always had the strange ability to cut my spirit armor so easily
this time though things have changed so you might as well accept that i won't die and you won't live
hear me zavkiel come to me now
daleto
your talent for healing is impressive i'm not healing in the least i'm simply turning back
the clock come fight let the fun begin sure bring it on i'll just kill you like i normally do
you still don't get it do you
try as much as you like but there's no way you'll ever be able to get rid of me completely
we'll see about that we'll see about that get ready to die
olive
mana
science
but how
mana no
kurumi
she's alive
please don't come any closer
shito
you're here
oh how sweet looks like everyone made it kurumi you're gonna pay for what you're doing here you can't
run from us
wow i'm positively terrified to attack poor little kurumi with so many people all at once
lucky for me though i'm playing for keeps
today
isn't that right
what the hell is all this
this is my past my dear shito my history they're beautiful aren't they
now do you understand why i can never fully be killed where did they all come from
time now we need to finish this
after you're gone i can be free there you go you should really stop getting your hopes up for me
shito i've taken some precautions to make sure you can't seduce me again
no you can't
prepare to be surrounded by so much death the last thing you'll want to save is me
please no
what is the meaning of this you mean you didn't know surprise surprise
spatial quakes can be neutralized if they run into a tremor of equal force at the onset
uh it's her what sis don't let me forget to give this back to you shito
burn
bro what do you say are you about ready to begin our date
is
Thank you.